现在我们已经完成一些了。接下来要做的就是在onCreate()函数最后面
Well now we're getting somewhere. All we have to do is run those table creation
调用execSQL来执行这些表的创建语句。等一下
queries by calling execSQL at the end of our on create function. But wait,
在这里有SQLiteOpenHelper的另一个函数，onUpgrade()。你可能会想
there's another function in our SQLiteOpenHelper, onUpgrade. You might think,
为什么我要在意这个？
why should I care about those?
我还没更新任何东西呢。为了让我们的开发更简单
I'm not upgrading anything yet. To make our development lives easier we're
我们准备在这里实现下标准的onUpgrade()
going to implement the most standard kind of onUpgrade there is.
你看，onUpgrade()只会在你改变数据库版本时候触发
You see onUpgrade only fires if you change the version of your database.
注意，我们之前就把版本传递进了SQliteOpenHelper的基本构造器
Now remember, we passed that version into the SQliteOpenHelper base constructor,
因为我们将数据库用作一个缓存来保存网络数据
ages ago. Since we are going to be using our database as a cache for web data
而不是用户产生数据，所以我们会扔掉这个表。如果我们以后想修改数据库
and not for user generated content, we'll drop the tables. This is helpful if we
这很有用处。如果我们用用户数据
want to change the database in the future. If we were using user data, we'd do
我们不会这么做，而是比如说改变下表，加一个新列之类的。所以，数据库完成了。
something like use alter table to add new columns. So, now we have a database.